(The Talk of the Town)
Nice to see you, everyone.
It's been a while, Lee Jung.
- Gosh, it's been a while. - Welcome.
- It's so nice to see you. - Hello.
How did your friends react after your episode aired?
A lot of my friends reached out to me.
My friends and acquaintances commented that...
I had a successful career now.
(Unlike her charismatic presence on the job,)
(she spent a wholesome day with Actor Roh Yoon Seo.)
(Her episode went viral thanks to her unexpected charm.)
(Lee Jung looks like a sweet girl. She's so kind and adorable.)
(Can you star on the show again? An hour was too short.)
- Dudu went viral too. - Right.
- He's such a cute dog. - Right.
- I also... Yes, he's so healthy. - Is he doing well?
He's still adorable.
What about the air conditioner?
- Oh, the air conditioner. - Yes.
- Did you fix it? - That also went viral.
(Startled)
- What? There's a leak. - What's going on?
(All of a sudden, water started to leak from the air conditioner.)
My landlord fixed the air conditioner...
- after watching my episode. - What?
- The landlord? - I see. The landlord?
- That's a relief. - Right.
We actually have more good news to share.
This year, our program won...
the Grand Award at the Brand of the Year Awards...
for four consecutive years...
in the observation-based variety show category.
- Thank you. - My gosh.
- Congratulations. - Winning it once is a huge feat.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
It's more meaningful...
because our program won it four years in a row.
We'll work harder to bring you more entertainment.
(We'll do our best to make a better show.)
(The Cheat Day of Self-Esteem)
(Someone is standing on her toes.)
Gosh, that hurts.
(It's Na Rae?)
(Groaning)
- Gosh, that hurts a lot. - Why are you wearing...
- a military-issued shirt? - Why are you wearing that?
- Where did you get that shirt? - You can buy it in stores.
- I just bought it online. - There are military stores.
- Really? - Yes.
I thought you didn't return yours when you got discharged.
- Gosh, I must return everything. - You did, right?
That shirt is great for absorbing sweat.
- That's right. - It's so breathable.
- Is that so? - That's the best summer shirt.
It's super functional. I get hot easily.
- You know? Right. - And the snail cream.
That's the perfect color on you.
Right, that color is perfect.
I didn't even get pimples during puberty.
Why am I getting them when I'm 40?
(Sergeant Park is fighting a battle against the pimples.)
(Smothered)
- I shouldn't have touched them. - Why not wear the camouflage cream?
I put on some wash-off face mask.
My skin has been acting up lately.
(Grabbing)
(Giggling)
It came out nicely.
(Staring)
(Looking around)
This looks amazing. I want to do this right.
- I wish it was a bit bigger. - What's that?
- My gosh. That photo. - It's your wedding photo.
That would've been the perfect size.
A lot of people made seaweed soup after watching this episode.
People have been talking about this for quite some time.
(She carefully displays it in her house.)
This looks good.
But it looks a bit small.
That's a great picture.
I got it in a small size.
- You did that on purpose? - Yes.
Yes, it looks beautiful.
(Yes, it looks beautiful.)
(Staring)
It came out nicely.
I really wanted to get that developed.
- You had to. - It's a great picture.
- Right, I had to. - Of course.
It's like a photo from a magazine.
Wear that to the year-end awards ceremony.
- That's not a bad idea. - As the broom-to-be?
- Isn't it a good idea? - That's a great concept.
Upgrade the broom-to-be outfit and wear it to the ceremony.
- Yes. - I can do that.
Wear a men's hairstyle.
- Get the buzz cut? - Get the buzz cut.
- Get the buzz cut. - Get the buzz cut.
- Like the two-block haircut. - As the broom-to-be.
Remember the villain in "Mazinger Z?"
- Baron Ashura? - Baron Ashura. Yes.
- What's going on? - Yes.
- Half of it. - Half man and half woman.
(Her broom-to-be concept is improving.)
Come on.
This looks hip.
(She goes downstairs after displaying her photo.)
She does look like a commissioned officer.
She's getting nostalgic at the military locker.
The military locker?
- What? - Is someone in your house?
(She hurriedly grabs a few beverage cans.)
(Glancing)
(People are moving around busily in her house.)
- Are you renovating your house? - Gosh.
(They're even utilizing professional equipment.)
That's to keep the line parallel.
(Outdoor Ad Installation Agency)
Why is there an agency for installing outdoor ads?
What reason could they possibly have to be at her house?
The outdoor ads...
(The construction site seems unusual.)
This is all I have to offer you in the house.
- Have a cool drink while working. - Thank you.
- Have a drink. - Gosh, hello.
- Hello. - I'm a fan.
Gosh, thank you.
By the way, it is indeed huge.
What's huge?
It's like an artwork.
- What's that? - What is that?
This puts me in a solemn mood.
What's that?
(Overwhelming)
Come on.
Having that in your home is the same as Hyun Moo having his leaves.
(Moomoo brought tree leaves into his home.)
Come on. This is completely different.
Don't insult my tree leaves.
They can purify the air, at least.
Seriously. They're both on the extreme ends.
This is coming right from my heart.
- Are you trying to battle me? - What do you mean? How absurd.
Recently,
I created an art piece with my concept as the broom-to-be.
I wanted to celebrate my piece in a proper manner.
This guy is almost an expert in this kind of field.
Ro Hong Chul referred me to this agency.
- He can be really excessive. - Right.
There's a famous artist in the world of neon signs.
He said this artist might be able to execute my vision.
So I personally sent him a direct message.
That's how I ended up with this art piece.
Did you also install lightbulbs?
- Yes. The neon signs. - The lights...
- Oh, no. - Hong Chul said...
he wanted to work with this artist.
But he never got a chance to do that.
He told me I should have a meeting with him.
That's how he introduced me to Mr. Neon.
- Mr. Neon. - Yes.
Your house already attracts a lot of bugs.
- You'll turn on those lights? - My gosh.
They will attract moths.
Her wedding picture...
crossed over to modern art.
I can use the neon signs to portray my chest hair.
(Horrified)
Your chest hair will curl up. No.
- You'll burn your chest hair. - How many strands will you need?
(Moomoo wants to dabble in modern art too.)
This is great. I love it.
- We wanted to make it the biggest. - Yes.
But we still had to bring it in.
- Remember how we measured the door? - Yes.
This was the biggest size your door allowed.
The size must be over 400.
The height is 3m.
The width is 2m.
That's huge indeed.
I love it because it looks like a painting.
- Right. - Yes.
I didn't use the regular materials for this. I got it on a canvas.
(No wonder!)
- It looks like a painting more so. - I see.
- You've painted several times. - Right.
It has a similar texture from that.
This is great.
(The last step of pulling it upright keeps them busy.)
(Glancing)
Do you need help?
- When it's time to move this, - Yes.
I'd like to have a guy helping me.
I'm stronger than an average guy.
Don't you think I can help you?
- Sure. - Here comes Na Rae.
- You're dressed for a battle. - Right. My gosh.
I can totally help him.
(Sergeant Park sets out to back him up.)
(Opening)
(She wears a helmet for safety.)
- She's got everything at home. - She has everything.
I didn't know she had a helmet at home.
- The helmet... - I have one too.
- I have 3 helmets. - Why do you have 3 helmets?
- I ride the bicycle. - I see, the bicycle.
Depending on my mood, I sometimes want to wear...
a pink one, a white one, or a black one.
- That's important. Yes. - Right. Yes.
(She wears the military helmet to match with her personal color.)
Why does the helmet look like a combat helmet?
- "Trainee 156 Jun Hyun Moo." - Right.
- You're wearing a helmet? - Of course.
I have all kinds of tools at home.
You have to hold that part. Could you help her?
- Where? - Hold it.
- Should I hold it here? - Do we have to lay it flat?
- Yes. Come to the middle. - Okay.
(Na Rae is supporting the back.)
- I see. It's set up on the back. - Yes.
Hold it like that. One, two.
(Grunting)
- Keep coming. - My gosh.
Right here.
(It's like moving a real art piece from a museum.)
(Carefully moving it)
Seriously.
That's huge.
(Four people are struggling to carry it due to the large size.)
Turn it. Sir, you have to go that way.
- They're turning it. - Yes.
This is good.
(Struggling)
Hold on.
(Amazed)
(It looks even larger standing upright.)
The giraffe looks small in comparison.
Right.
(Eye-catching)
(Even Na Rae is amazed by the size.)
(He places down the ladder after moving it.)
(Rattling)
(Pulling up)
(Again?)
(The ladder keeps on going up.)
I used that ladder when I painted the mural.
It's going up now. One, two.
(The art piece is soaring higher.)
I see. He has to drill in every hole for this.
They will have to attach it firmly.
They must secure it firmly.
Who usually orders a canvas as big as this?
- The NMK. - Pardon?
The NMK.
The NMK?
The National Museum of Korea.
You'd see canvases as big as this at the museum.
I'd see canvases as big as this at the museum?
You could see a piece as big as this there.
Of course. Or the Museum of Modern and Contemporary Art.
(Amazed)
I haven't seen a painting as big as that at exhibits.
Same here. That's huge.
When I decided to get this done,
I also decided to do it exactly how I wanted.
So I went all out with this.
Right. It's better to do it with your photo,
- not someone else's. - But this is so cool. I mean it.
Thanks.
Now, I understand why they invited Lee Jung today.
Without her...
She's the only one who will side with Na Rae.
But think about it.
It's a healthy way of spending money.
I could be small,
- but I could dream big, right? - Yes.
- Of course. - Yes.
It looks so holy.
Gosh, it's making me feel holy.
It made me think at least I ought to love myself.
(Chuckling)
How about a lighting ceremony?
A lighting ceremony.
- Should I proceed? - Yes.
Everyone, look forward to it.
I really can't wait.
(This looks like a real opening ceremony.)
I'm curious.
(A nerve-racking moment)
(With everyone watching...)
(Focused)
(it's almost time for the highlight.)
(At last!)
(The lights are on.)
(Impressed)
(Giant Broom-to-be)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
(Flashy lights)
Na Rae became a deity.
(Naphrodite has descended with a flash.)
- Thank you so much. - Seeing it light up...
must have made you feel good.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Sir. I have a question.
Do you have a title for this piece?
You can make the sentence...
- on the canvas the title. - What does it say?
- "I'm grateful to be myself." - Yes.
That's all about self-esteem.
"I'm grateful to be myself."
That's right.
- "I'm happy that I'm me." - Yes.
- That's right. - Right.
It makes me so happy that I'm Park Na Rae.
Yes.
Why are you laughing at me?
Can I say something discouraging?
What is it?
People with real high self-esteem won't do things like that.
You...
He got me.
But this is all great if this is a step...
- toward high self-esteem. - Right.
- Really? - It's gorgeous.
The overwhelming sensation...
- It's beautiful. - The colors look so pretty.
Gosh, it came out so nicely.
(It's still captivating even from afar.)
This is amazing.
(I'm hooked on myself.)
I do think you're ahead of your time.
It does have that cyberpunk feel.
- Cyberpunk? - That's right.
- Can your electricity support it? - Yes.
- Can it handle the sign? - Yes, totally.
This is a misconception about neon signs.
People assume the signs eat up a lot of electricity.
- Right. - It consumes as much electricity...
- as half a fridge section. - Right.
I didn't know it was energy-efficient.
I don't know how other people will see it.
But it made me feel solemn and gave off a holy vibe.
It's the peak of self-esteem.
Hyun Moo always displays his trophies at home.
He blows up his own picture.
Gosh, what's wrong with my face?
Nothing compares to this.
This... How is he going to copy this?
This could be hanging at the NMK.
(This is my own National Museum.)
In other words, this is my treasure as well as Korea's.
That's what it is to me.
(The history of Korea is embedded at the National Museum of Korea.)
(Just like the precious treasures in the museum...)
They'll insert this to her clip?
(A massive neon-sign piece of Na Rae at her house)
(Treasure 1 of Na Rae's Museum)
It could be hanging at a museum...
- a few centuries later. - Right.
When people come over to my house, I'll be their docent.
"Let me explain to you about this piece."
"It shows that I overcame all of the crises from the world."
"The more you carve it, the more beautiful it becomes."
I'll scam people that I drew that.
(Do you understand?)
Aphrodite was born from a shell.
Na Rae is blooming from the shell.
"Keep taking shots at me."
"I'm Shelly Broom-to-be."
What does that mean?
"Na Rae who was born like a pearl."
- I see. So you got an upgrade? - Yes.
- Gosh, that sounds a bit off. - "Shelly Broom-to-be?"
Here's an explanation. I'm the descendant of Hyeok Geo Se.
- You? - The man who hatched from an egg.
- Since you have the same last name? - Right. Of course.
- So I'm Shelly Broom-to-be. - Shelly Broom-to-be?
By the way, you do things on a different scale.
- That's the worst-sounding name. - It looks beautiful too.
- Thank you. I knew it. - Shelly Broom-to-be?
- A lot of people want to do it. - Shelly Broom-to-be?
- But they just can't. - I have...
- a good eye for things like this. - Lee Jung.
Are you cool with the name?
Shelly Broom-to-be?
- I'm okay as long as she's happy. - I'm so happy.
I'm happy to be myself.
(She barely manages to sympathize.)
- Please wrap this up for me. - Sure.
This is great because we can't see your face clearly.
Come on.
(After the installation, she comes out with arm sleeves.)
(She's also carrying the cleaning equipment too.)
(What's she going to do next?)
Are you done with the installation?
Yes. They're cleaning up.
Yes.
They sent out some military support.
(Like the reliable soldiers from the military support...)
My gosh. Seriously.
This will be the peak season for mosquitoes.
I have to spray the mosquito and larvae repellent.
I need to water my crops.
Persimmons keep on falling off.
This is the busiest season for me.
(Sighing)
- This is when I have the most work. - This is the peak season.
(She feels intimidated even before she begins.)
What a mess, seriously.
(What a mess, seriously.)
(Na Rae's ultimate dream while having a garden)
(The open-air bathtub with clear, pure water)
Gosh, this is the perfect size.
I was so happy then.
(Right now, it's a mess.)
Gosh. Oh, no.
What's that?
(Covered in leaves and dust)
Why didn't you put a cover on it?
It's much messier than I expected.
(This looks worse than I anticipated.)
What a royal mess.
- What will you do with this? - Gosh.
This is how it looks when I don't clean for ten days.
- They're rotten. - They kept falling off.
(The persimmons on the ground are rotting away.)
What could you do?
Gosh, this...
(Brimming with resentment toward the persimmon tree)
(She was happy when she was enjoying the fruit.)
We plucked so many of those...
- two years ago. - Right.
Nothing is going right without Kian84.
I'm sorry.
(It's time to cherish the garden like she cherishes herself.)
This is completely ruined.
It's way too hot in summer, so it's impossible to use that.
I don't go out there in summer.
(It's fully covered with leaves and dust.)
(Na Rae tries to sweep up the leaves.)
When will you finish everything?
How will you remove the moss?
That?
I can use a toothbrush.
A toothbrush?
A long time ago, people used to put toothpaste on a toothbrush...
To clean?
Have you served in the military?
I used to do that when the commander was coming.
How does she know all this?
It started out as a joke. But how do you know all this?
She remembers the military service better than us.
- That's a detailed memory. - How do you know that?
(Just like how she was taught in the military,)
(she digs up the leaves from a hard-to-reach corner.)
(She gets down on the ground and collects the leaves.)
Darn it.
(Groaning)
(As she endures the late summer's heat...)
Gosh. I mean, it looked great when she set it up.
Darn it. This is so annoying.
This is annoying.
Hold on.
This isn't going anywhere.
(This isn't going anywhere.)
(Hold on, let me think.)
(I should try using this.)
I'm finally using it after neglecting it for two years.
(An excellent idea that could help her cleaning)
Yes. I was wondering...
- why you didn't use that. - What's that?
- It's an air blower. - An air blower.
(An air blower)
I see. You have that at home.
Here's the thing. To live in a house with a garden,
- I... - You need that.
- I can't hire people every time... - You really need that.
- to get something done. - You must have that.
You do things on a grand scale.
(I can see hope.)
Yes, just like that.
Great. Gosh, this...
What is this?
- Do you have to charge it? - You must charge it.
- No. Charging... - Did you not charge the battery?
(What is it? What's wrong?)
What? I had to buy the battery separately?
Why didn't it come with the battery?
You must have not added that while choosing the option.
- Is that it? - It's always in the options.
No wonder why it was so cheap.
(It doesn't have a battery.)
This would be perfect for this job.
It's useless without the battery.
Sir, do you have the same battery for this air blower?
- Yes. - Thank you.
- I'll return it quickly. - He had it.
Gosh, you had it. Thank you.
(Please work.)
- Is it compatible? - Was it the perfect fit?
Is it not working?
- It's not compatible. - Really?
Right, it can't be compatible.
He had a professional one.
But I didn't. So it didn't fit.
Gosh, I have to do everything since I live here.
(I'll have to sweep everything then.)
(She tries her best to sweep up the leaves.)
(There's no giving up despite the unfavorable condition.)
This song...
This is a familiar scene.
That's why I feel awful when I see soldiers...
shoveling snow.
(She misses her fellow soldiers as she works alone.)
Come on. There are cockroaches.
Gosh, those house centipedes.
- Cockroaches? - Yes.
(I must overcome the cockroaches too.)
Did you grab them with your hands?
Of course, I had to use my hands.
A piece of tissue and dead insects...
- Of course. It's fine. - look about the same to us...
because there are too many of them.
I should clean proactively next time.
(This time, she's cleaning the moss.)
(Cleaning zealously)
(The moss is coming off gradually.)
Right, the tub was covered in moss.
Gosh, it looks like matcha latte.
Match latte?
- That's a trendy drink now. - Yes.
What do I do with this?
It's clogged.
- Of course, it will be clogged. - This is a disaster.
(This is a disaster.)
(What is this now?)
(She didn't think the drain would be clogged.)
- Why did it get clogged? - Gosh.
- The leaves. - It was because of the leaves.
Did they get tangled up in there?
They didn't install a proper drain.
I have to call in an expert.
(She's sweating profusely.)
I was going to use it starting next week.
(The open-air bathtub is hopeless.)
(She starts cleaning the fallen persimmons.)
I should have invited Hyun Moo.
If he saw this,
he wouldn't have mentioned moving to a single-family home.
I really wanted to call you over.
(Hyun Moo has secretly been envious of Na Rae's garden.)
(When he went to look at houses last time,)
(he was fixated on single-family homes and gardens.)
I don't mind having a lot of things to do. I can do them.
But I hate bugs.
This is the reality.
(Conflicted)
(The persimmons rotted while lying on the deck.)
(She keeps raking them in as her face heats up.)
They were stuck on the deck.
- So it was hard to get them off. - Right, it's hard.
(Nothing is easy about cleaning the garden.)
(Retching)
(Groaning)
(Grossed out)
(She can't stop gagging.)
So listen.
Gosh, thinking about it makes me nauseous again.
- Oh, no. - The thought of it...
The viewers will understand my reaction...
once they can start smelling the same thing.
Here's the thing about persimmons.
They keep falling off from July to September.
I'm talking about those tiny ones.
If they just fall off, they wouldn't be my problem.
- But they rot. - They get bruised.
Then they get sour like persimmon vinegar.
On top of that, they start growing fur...
like fleece.
- When they get moldy? - I see. They get moldy.
Then they exude a rotten smell.
(Gagging)
(A blowfly follows her because of the smell.)
My gosh, come on. That little jerk.
- Seriously. - Blowflies keep coming to me.
I thought the blowfly was a drone camera.
- Those blowflies are huge. - It was as big as a drone camera?
Seriously. It was this big.
It must've been growing in her house.
So they keep crashing into the window.
Thud.
- I'm serious. - That's true.
- To come into your house? - I know what you're talking about.
- Yes. - Those big ones...
- They must be half-crazy. - Right.
(But I hate blowflies.)
- That's too much. - You're showing me this clip,
so I don't move to a single-family home, right?
No.
(He still can't give up on a house with a garden.)
I feel like throwing up.
(The reality of living in a house with a garden)
Should I pull out the tree for real?
Should I just remove the tree?
But you kept it on purpose.
Right. It's 30 years old.
Right, it's a magical tree.
- Gosh, her house... - She has so many things at home.
I really thought I might die that day.
I see how you never have a day off.
Let's try to think this brings me joy.
I'm happy.
Gosh, I'm very happy.
What? Are they done?
Sir.
Did you finish?
Gosh, thank you for everything.
Okay.
- Mr. Neon is leaving. - I'll get going.
Thank you.
Gosh, I'll take a short break.
It's so cool inside.
Gosh, my house is absolute paradise.
(Na Rae grabs water and snack for her break.)
I did that on an empty stomach.
I started to retch toward the end.
You'll get a dizzy spell.
(She drags her fatigued body outside into the heat.)
I should have the low-sugar jeolpyeon.
- Oh, that? - So you know about that rice cake.
Of course.
(She quickly has a bite.)
(She can't stop taking bites of it.)
(Humming)
(She grabs another one right away.)
(Chewy texture)
It's tasty.
- It's peanut-butter flavored. - Peanut-butter flavored?
- You should've brought one. - Gosh, I'm sorry.
- You could've brought some. - Right.
(I'll eat up all the tasty food by myself.)
This is tasty.
(Munching)
She's eating it like it's a combat ration.
A combat ration?
It's tasty.
They make good rice cakes.
(The snack is right up Sergeant Park's alley.)
(Let me go back to cleaning.)
What's that?
(Turning on the electric drill)
(She keeps bringing in industrial tools.)
Gosh, what's that?
(She strides over after fully getting ready.)
Gosh, this is a big mess.
Darn.
I paid a lot of money for this.
What?
(The pride of Korea, the National Museum of Korea)
(National and Na Rae's Treasure 1, "Shelly Broom-to-be,")
(is followed by Treasure 2.)
As for the cauldron lid,
I used it often during spring.
I grilled pork belly on it.
I also braised chicken in it.
I should have brought it inside.
But it got rusted during the rainy season.
It really is a mess.
Once it rusts,
no matter how hard you try, you can't remove the rust.
As for the tool I used,
I could hook it up with the drill and use it on the lid.
This can remove the rust.
It becomes as good as new.
- My gosh. - That? I see.
I can grind the iron with that.
- I see. You can remove a layer? - Yes.
Gosh, it's coming off. This is amazing.
(I'll knock you out.)
This hits the spot.
(She picks up the drilling speed.)
The left side now.
(It's time to rinse off the lid with a water hose.)
It's not working.
I need to do it four times.
My gosh.
It looks like a loach.
That's like when dogs are happy to see people.
(Turning)
Darn.
(She barely manages to turn off the water.)
(She's at the end of her rope.)
(But she must finish cleaning.)
- More persimmons are falling off. - Gosh.
Will you move into a single-family home?
The idea started to sound less attractive.
I can see that you're actually angry.
My gosh.
Come on. There it goes again.
It's cute, though.
You should raise it like a pet.
How cute.
(She barely manages to calm down her pet hose.)
Let's just do it.
(She starts rinsing off the deck with newfound determination.)
(She tries to clean the cauldron lid again.)
(Thoroughly washing it)
Usually, it only takes two cycles to clean this completely.
But it looks much better now.
- It looks clean. - The rust...
- is gone. Yes. - It looks good.
(She finishes cleaning the yard after two hours.)
(Drained)
It wasn't just sunny that day, seriously.
It was hot and humid. You know?
On days like that, you sweat even when you do nothing.
(I gave my all.)
(Grabbing)
What's that now?
- A sprinkler to water the plants. - Is it a sprinkler?
(Gushing out)
What's she doing? Is she taking it off?
(She approaches it with a determined look.)
(Smirking)
(She splashes it on herself, not the plants.)
You wash off your body outdoors more than men.
(She washes her hair boldly like a confident woman.)
(Or is she washing her waist?)
- Gosh. What's that? - My gosh.
This must be your vacation seeing how you have a swim ring on.
- You look like the Michelin Man. - Yes.
- You went on your summer vacation. - Yes.
My gosh. But everyone has some love handles.
I like this side of myself too. I find myself lovable.
No one said anything.
She's desperately defending herself.
- We didn't say anything. - Right. What?
(Today,)
(I'll spend the whole day, loving myself.)
(Whizzing)
(What's she doing?)
(She's rinsing her teeth.)
- Why is she rinsing her mouth here? - I can't believe I must watch this.
(A refreshing and fun way to floss without lifting a finger)
- It actually fell off. - You're right.
What happened?
(A remnant of the snack she just had)
- A peanut particle flew off. - Yes.
I see that it has many functions.
- Of course. - It has a flossing function.
(I see that it can remove food particles effectively.)
Kian84, you should borrow it...
to floss your buttocks.
Okay. If you lend me that item, I'll use it on my buttocks.
It'll be true friendship.
(The cool flossing time ends.)
- It was a solo Waterbomb Festival. - Yes.
(My goodness)
Gosh, what's up with these eggplants?
How did I get so many eggplants?
(The place Na Rae loves as much as herself)
It's truly a mystery.
There are only eight roots, but the eggplants come out sturdy.
- They're sturdy. - What?
How are they so big?
Does gravity work differently...
- in this house? - I don't know.
They look like spoon worms.
- Those eggplants look a bit scary. - They look so strange.
- That's a boomerang. - It's so big.
Who was the Japanese cartoon artist Kian84 liked?
- He'd like those eggplants. - Ito Junji.
Those eggplants have that vibe.
At my place,
- I just need to sow the seeds. - The soil must be nice.
- The crops become huge. - They grow on their own.
Seriously.
The energy of the land must be nice because the plants grow well.
It isn't the fertile soil of the Honam region's fields.
I just gave them water once every three days.
Look at the basil plant.
The soil must be nice there.
It must be very fertile.
Na Rae, you should plant your feet in the soil.
Her feet will become this big.
Her feet will become 310mm.
For goodness' sake.
Gosh, what's up with these eggplants?
(Na Rae stands before the king-sized eggplants.)
Gosh, this is...
(Shall I pick them?)
(She harvests a big eggplant.)
I've never seen such an eggplant in my life.
(Picking)
What's going on?
It looks like a club.
You should give them to the police officers.
(She goes back into the house with the club-looking eggplants.)
I'm hungry.
How are these eggplants so big?
(She brings a big eggplant to the sink.)
(Squeaky clean)
(She cuts off the stem.)
It doesn't go in because it's so big.
I should put it on the top.
(She places it on the bowl and moves it to the microwave.)
- Will you microwave it? - Yes.
(That's right.)
People make a lot of eggplant dishes...
these days.
There was a recipe which cooked eggplants like eels.
- I made rice with eggplant. - Rice with eggplant?
Rice with eggplant is tasty.
I'd be full after eating one eggplant.
(Na Rae's rice with eggplant recipe will be revealed.)
(Na Rae harvested a king-sized eggplant.)
I microwaved it for three minutes.
Then I cut it open and spread it wide.
It looks delicious.
It has been cooked well.
All right.
Oh, my.
(The spread eggplant goes into the oiled pan.)
I thought it was a mackerel.
(Laughing)
- You cook it like an eel. - An eel?
Eggplants are soggy, right?
- So, - It's a good idea.
sprinkling starch on the top...
makes it chewier and crunchier.
Many people don't eat eggplants because of that.
- That's right. - The soggy texture.
(She makes it sticky.)
Soy sauce, allulose, and tuna sauce.
At the end, I add a bit of doubanjiang.
You make rice with eggplant in a unique way.
(She quickly makes scrambled eggs.)
I put scrambled eggs over the rice.
Then I top it with the eggplant. That's the rice with eggplant.
The recipe is doable because it's simple.
- It looks tasty. - It looks like rice with eel.
(I'll eat it with side dishes.)
It looks tasty.
- My mom's young radish kimchi. - Young radish kimchi.
It's nicely aged.
Let's eat.
(The reward for her hard work is rice with king-sized eggplant.)
(She takes a big spoonful.)
(Her eyes go wide.)
(Taking another spoonful)
(This is the taste I wanted.)
It must be tasty.
(His mouth waters.)
I was surprised by how tasty it was.
It's so tasty.
It looks tasty.
(Slurping)
(Food tastes even better after hard work.)
(It's so tasty!)
What's that in the back? Is that a soldier or what?
- In the back... - Is that a commander?
(A quick promotion)
Excuse me?
A war hero.
(Their attention is on the war hero.)
(Picking up)
What?
- ATEEZ? - It's my favorite video.
- Do you like ATEEZ? - I love ATEEZ.
- Really? - You like ATEEZ.
I've watched their videos so many times.
I really want to go to the pre-recording.
I want to go to their concert too.
(Smiling)
(She watches them from the 1st row at home.)
I want to go to the pre-recording.
My bias is...
- a team called ATEEZ. - ATEEZ.
I like SAN so much.
When he takes the stage,
he becomes a grand duke of the north of romance fantasy novels.
He has controlled charms.
That video is my absolute favorite!
How are his shoulders so broad?
When you reach this age,
it isn't easy to become obsessed with something.
There's only one thing I want from my darlings.
- I want them to be happy. - "My darlings?"
Aren't they about ten years younger than you?
No, they're my darlings.
(SAN was born in 1999, but he's my darling.)
You sound like a soldier who is talking about a girl group.
- All handsome men are darlings. - I agree.
(Just as she loves her darlings,)
(she loves her meal.)
(She finishes a huge eggplant...)
(in an instant.)
I finished it.
- It must've been very tasty. - It was a huge eggplant.
You should go to her place to get some eggplants.
- I'd love to do that. - You should come.
- You live in Yongsan. - Yes, I live in Yongsan.
Why are you laughing?
We've watched your video.
- You don't cook. - No.
- So, why do you want eggplants? - Why do you want eggplants?
- You don't even cook. - That's right.
- Why do you want them? - They'll be like souvenirs.
- Souvenirs? - Souvenirs.
They won't last.
- Souvenirs from Na Rae. - You know,
- that eggplant could be a souvenir. - Thank you.
Use it for self-defense.
- Self-defense. - Self-defense.
(It's sturdy, so use it for self-defense.)
(Instead of using it for self-defense,)
(she enjoyed the eggplant.)
(She goes somewhere after doing the dishes.)
What's that?
Things keep coming out.
(Items keep coming out.)
Will you do the tea ceremony?
You drink tea.
Why would you do the tea ceremony when the weather is so hot?
There's tea I'm obsessed with these days.
What is it?
(She brings an array of ingredients for tea.)
Will you add whipped cream to tea?
That's a tiramisu ingredient.
Is that tiramisu?
That cheese is a tiramisu ingredient.
- I see. - Mascarpone.
What?
(Milk?)
Gosh, I know what this is.
Matcha latte?
I've become obsessed with matcha.
(Hue Park is also in love with it.)
(Matcha latte is all the rage in New York.)
That was why I was surprised.
What I made just now was...
the matcha tiramisu latte.
Tiramisu.
I use oat milk instead of milk.
It's more savory.
I feel like I'm eating tiramisu.
However, it isn't greasy.
Give me the recipe. How do you make it?
- Oat milk. - Oat milk.
Then in a matcha bowl...
- You whisk matcha. - Yes.
To that...
Do you just mix it in?
You create layers...
- by pouring it in slowly. - You create layers.
Just you wait.
(This is how you give colors to each layer.)
I'll aim for it.
You'll aim for it?
How pretty.
(Attentive)
(She rewards herself with a dessert for her hard work.)
This is the taste I want.
(Like a New Yorker, she enjoys...)
(a rare moment of relaxation.)
It must be really tasty.
(Jealous)
(Today, she was busy taking care of herself.)
Cleaning up the house took so much time.
The entire day passed.
What? Hold on.
Did "Comedy Big League" come back to life?
What are you saying?
- Why would it come back to life? - Didn't that happen?
Where are you going this time?
Will she enter a wrestling match?
Back in the day, I didn't even wear pants.
- I went outside that way. - Why did you forgo pants?
That sounds nice. The weather is hot anyway.
- Her clothes are very plain today. - They're plain.
- You know... - To be honest, I was disappointed.
- Now that I'm old... - Her outfit is very modest.
Now that I'm old, I've changed.
I thought you were going to the meeting of the parents.
Seriously.
(It's hard to tell where she's going from her outfit.)
National Museum of Korea.
(Shelly Broom-to-be pays respect to the work of art.)
It's like the National Museum of Korea.
(It's a museum, not a house.)
Her back is open.
My back looks nice. My back looks pretty.
It's Gyeongnidan-gil.
(She walks down Gyeongnidan-gil...)
(confidently.)
Today, my outfit was a bit ordinary.
But the back was the important part.
Jeans and a white T-shirt?
Ordinary outfits really don't suit me.
When I wear an outfit like that,
I love becoming absorbed in myself.
I come to love myself more.
I love that a different side of me comes out.
(I always discover a new side of myself.)
- It's important. - Yes.
When you wear an outfit you like,
you become confident.
- You can be yourself the most. - So,
when I drink alcohol at home,
I wear a dress even if I'm by myself.
That's good. When I'm home,
I don't necessarily wear comfy clothes.
I'm sorry, but "That's good" was a bit slow just now.
It isn't like that.
You were wearing very comfortable clothes at home.
Seriously, I'm the same.
I don't wear a dress.
But even at home, I wear the clothes I like.
I don't focus solely on comfort.
"That's good" came after a pause.
(She gets a pass for relating to Na Rae.)
Na Rae!
Na Rae, we love you!
I love you too.
See you around.
People in Itaewon...
are passionate.
- They were strangers, right? - Yes.
- Right? - The neighborhood is like that.
That's right. It's always like that.
(She walks down the street in a fancy outfit.)
(Impressed)
(My goodness)
It's packed.
Hello.
- Come on in. It has been a while. - It has been a while, right?
- Hello. - Hello.
Oh, my. I can't believe it.
- I can't believe you're here. - Sister.
- Sister. - Oh, my. Sister.
- Who is she? - My friends in the neighborhood.
- Your friends in the neighborhood? - Yes.
Have you been well?
(The owner checks in with her.)
This is the bar I frequent.
I visited for the first time after moving.
so I've been going for about three years.
Many Itaewon and Gyeongnidan-gil residents go there.
It's very atmospheric.
When you eat alone, you feel very miserable.
But when you drink alone,
it feels very atmospheric.
And here's the important part. In my neighborhood,
you never feel like you're drinking alone.
Even when you go alone, it doesn't feel that way.
They talk to you...
and ask you to drink with them.
I befriend people that way.
I love it so much...
that I visit quarterly.
What have you been drinking?
- Old fashioned? - What will you drink?
Hold on.
- Can you make a dirty martini? - Of course.
- Okay. - All right.
Is dirty martini the cocktail with crushed ice?
No, it contains olives.
It's a bit salty.
You have a conversation other people can join, right?
When I go to a place like that...
"How old are you? What do you do for a living?"
After we become close, I go,
"Hey, you shouldn't live that way."
- What are you talking about? - The moment you do that,
you'll get kicked out of the neighborhood.
What are you, a village teacher?
"You shouldn't be drinking, you punk."
It's natural to drink at a bar, you punk.
I end up doing that.
"You need to come to your senses."
Why do you even go to a bar?
When people stare, I go, "What are those punks looking at?"
"What are those punks looking at?" Come on.
- That's an old expression. - You're too old to be like that.
I have a different mindset.
You're so open-minded, Na Rae.
It's so hot.
(Glancing over)
Hello.
This place is great.
(She says hello to the customers across the table.)
- She's fluent in Korean. - Really?
- Her name is Da Som. - Hello.
- What? - She's Korean.
- Really? - She's a naturalized citizen.
Really? Are you a naturalized citizen?
Na Rae, don't you remember me?
We drank together last time.
- We had met. - That's right.
I went to Turkiye afterward.
I know. I watched all the episodes.
My goodness.
I was like, "That's my country."
Oh, my.
They're handsome, right?
You know, men in the Old Town were quite nice.
It was so nice.
She's Im Da Som.
- She's a naturalized citizen. - Im Da Som?
- Yes. - Im Da Som?
Yes. When she became naturalized, she took the last name of Im.
She's the first member of the Yongsan Im Clan.
She's the progenitor.
Really?
They were fine.
Here's your special martini.
Thank you.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Cheers. - Salute.
- Salute. - It's so hip.
(They do cheers and drink together.)
(My goodness)
This is the best. This is the taste I wanted.
You should come to my place...
and take some lettuce.
Do you grow lettuce at home?
I grow eggplants, lettuce, basil,
chives...
They must be hard to grow.
But the eggplants...
I only have one eggplant plant.
From a single plant, eight eggplants came out.
It's so weird.
Don't say that it's weird.
Did the plant bear fruits?
Yes, it did. I picked one.
You must be interested.
I gave her eggplants.
Hey, Turkiye. Let's have a drink.
- Let's have a drink. Okay. - I'd love that.
She's so fluent in Korean.
My goodness.
- Thank you. - You received it with both hands.
(Im Da Som knows the Korean etiquette.)
It's nice to meet you.
Salute.
(Although she came alone, she clinks glasses with others.)
- Everyone, be happy. - All right.
Na Rae looks so happy.
I'm so happy.
I love my neighborhood so much.
Today, I was a farmer at home.
Outside,
I was the empress.
For goodness' sake.
I like who I am.
I really like that I'm Park Na Rae.
I like everything.
This is the Itaewon freedom.
- It's hot. - It's hot.
My goodness. Stay healthy.
- Salute. - Salute.
- Health and happiness. - Health and happiness.
(I'm Happy That I'm Na Rae)
(I Live Alone)
Will this person be reincarnated?
(Sokcho Express Bus Terminal)
- It's Gangwon Province. - Sokcho.
Will this person go to Yangyang?
(Someone visits the Sokcho Express Bus Terminal.)
Gosh, what's up with this weather?
Gosh, he became so fit.
He has bulked up.
That's right. His chest became huge.
I gained 10kg.
(His chest is pumped up.)
- The shirt fits differently. - You look so cool.
That's right. You've changed completely.
- You definitely look healthy today. - Yes.
- The shirt fits differently. - I know.
- It's nice to hear the compliments. - I mean...
You look like Captain America.
(Captain Jae Hyeon came back with a new body.)
The sleeves fit snugly around his arms.
- I know. He looks cool. - Gosh.
- What's that? - A toy?
He'll like it, right?
There must be a baby.
(He walks with a toy box that's the size of his body.)
Hello.
Let's punch in the address.
(He takes a taxi from the bus terminal.)
It has been a while.
He'll love it.
I'm getting excited already.
(Gosh!)
That bridge.
It's perfect.
It's nice.
Goseong?
I'm excited.
(He heads over to Goseong, a place where an exciting encounter awaits.)
You aren't from Goseong.
(He finally arrives at a place.)
Gosh.
(Laughing)
Where is he?
Min Ji.
Min Ji?
- Min Ji? - Min Ji.
Is she a relative?
Min Ji.
(He continues to call for someone.)
Si On?
Hello.
Is he a nephew?
- It's a baby. - Si On, hello.
- What's that? - How cute!
What's that?
Oh, my.
- Hello. - Hey.
- Si On, hello. - You brought a really big one.
- What? - Hey, Min Ji.
He brought it.
What are you going to do?
This is where a couple I know lives.
Jeon Min Ji is a friend I've known for 16 years.
Then there are her husband...
and her baby,
- He's a baby. - Si On.
- Si On. - These three are together.
Si On looks just like his mother.
I knew Min Ji...
since I first started working as a model.
She was a friend of the manager I worked with.
She always helped at the back when I had shows.
What was fascinating was that she was the same age as me.
There weren't many that were my age.
- That was how we became friends. - Really?
It has been four years...
since I visited Min Ji's house.
I visited before Min Ji got pregnant.
She then got pregnant and raised her child...
- until a stable period. - Right.
We just talked to each other often on the phone.
Now that Si On has grown a lot, I decided to visit.
You've known her for a long time.
- I should wash my hands. - You can wash them here.
(It's his first visit after his friend gave birth.)
Si On is so adorable. My goodness.
Why is Si On so big now?
You should greet him, Si On.
Make a bow to your uncle.
You should make a bow to your uncle.
Make a bow.
- Gosh! - No. To your uncle.
He was the one who bought it for you.
- Hi, Si On! - "Thank you."
There you go.
Say, "Thank you."
- Give him a hug. - Give him a hug.
- Si On. - Give him a hug.
- A hug should be given... - Give a kiss on the cheek too.
as he brought the gift.
(Slowly approaching)
It's great to see you, Si On.
He's going to someone he has never seen before.
Give me a hug.
- "Thank you." - How adorable.
(Screaming)
- Give him a kiss on the cheek. - My goodness.
- The child isn't shy. - How do you give him a kiss?
- The other side. - Gosh!
- The other side too. - Here?
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- Gosh! - You're done now. Come here.
(What do I do?)
- You're done. - Si On is so adorable!
- So adorable! - The child is really meek.
That would make you want to buy more gifts.
Exactly.
Is Si On popular with the boys?
- I guess so. - Si On?
- Yes. - Si On is popular with the girls.
- Si On is a boy. - What?
He's our son.
- He's your son? - What?
- Wasn't Si On your daughter? - He's our son.
- Si On! - Si On is a boy.
- He's a tough guy. - Right.
- Look at him stare at me. - He's staring.
(Si On is a tough guy!)
I thought he was a girl after looking at the pictures.
He's such a tough guy!
It does seem like he has a five o'clock shadow too.
Why would a kid have that?
- Here. - There's a reason...
for growing out his hair.
It's to make a donation.
Right. It was a stereotype to think of him as a girl.
How is the weather today?
I saw the beach earlier.
- The weather is great, - Right.
- but the waves... - They're a bit small.
- are a bit small. - They're small?
- They're Si On waves. - Si On waves.
We'll surf a bit.
- Surf? - So they'll be surfing.
You want to take your top off as you've been working out.
- Gosh. - At the end of summer.
You're super excited.
- Right. - You can show off your body now.
- I've gained a lot of strength. - Gosh.
When I first came and tried surfing four years ago,
I couldn't take off my wetsuit...
- as I was so exhausted. - Gosh. You were a water strider.
I've been working out a lot these days.
I thought that I would be able to do much better with surfing now.
I wanted to test myself.
I wanted to reveal my trained body...
as a true surfer.
You're ready now.
- We should get changed. - We should head out soon.
Let's get changed and head out.
- Let's go, Si On. - Take his hand.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Go! Let's go!
- Go! - Go!
Let's go!
- Can you lend me a wetsuit? - Sure.
- Let's get changed. - All right.
Okay.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- He's so big now. - Mr. Ahn Jae Hyeon!
- Why have you become so big? - Jae Hyeon!
- You have a great body. - He's so big now.
What happened?
(Jae Hyeon comes out after getting changed.)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- He's so big now. - Mr. Ahn Jae Hyeon!
- Why have you become so big? - Jae Hyeon!
- You have a great body. - He's so big now.
What happened?
You were my role model. You can't do this to me.
(Disappointed)
I'm really pale though, aren't I?
It would be much better with some tanning.
I should've brought him when I went for a tan.
The ant tan?
He would look amazing with some tanning.
Apply some Coke to him at home.
(He walks out with confidence.)
Gosh, he got so much bigger.
I have changed.
(The man with deficiency heat was very skinny.)
Deficiency heat?
The one that was skinny, weak,
and had cold hands?
My body feels hot now.
Around a month and a half ago,
the elevator of my apartment was under construction, right?
I went up and down the stairs like crazy...
for around a month.
He was really skinny back then.
I consistently worked out too.
I worked really hard.
I've been working out since then.
Well...
(Bulging out)
- Gosh! - Well...
He has fallen for his own muscles.
It was a body that I never had before in my life.
(Please be understanding.)
Gosh, I should work out my muscles.
After consistent workouts,
I have gained confidence.
I'm a real man now.
I have a lot of stamina now.
I will turn into a true surfer.
(I will turn into a true surfer.)
(I have been born again.)
(Reborn)
(Skinny and weak me,)
(it's time to say goodbye.)
(He is born again as a man full of stamina.)
A man full of stamina.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
He doesn't have a body to be making those faces yet.
He's not at that level yet.
It must be because your shoulders are wider now.
Come here.
(Spraying)
It's not cold.
Okay. Great.
I think you can put it on now.
My body looks a lot better now, right?
Right. Your shoulders are broader. You're looking great.
(Jae Hyeon gets changed with his help.)
- Gosh. - There you go.
It's perfect.
It feels like a leotard.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go. - Gosh.
(They get fully prepared.)
- The baby is wearing one too? - The baby is wearing one too?
- That's so cute. - It's been a while.
That's just so cute.
The husband and wife...
- met each other while surfing. - I see.
The scuba divers got together too.
Many people get together like that.
(Along with the romantic family of three)
The weather is great.
It's really peaceful.
(Off to the East Sea full of waves!)
When you watch Hollywood movies,
there are guys who surf while moving around...
- in their red trunks. - Right. This is it.
(The charming guys who move around the sea in their trunks.)
- What is this? - This is great footage.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
I really wanted to do that as well.
(Wait for me, tough waves.)
We're here.
- I think we can move there. - Where?
Here?
- The waves are quite small. - It's really calm.
It feels like a stream.
This is a lake.
There are no waves at all.
Surfers surf in fall or winter.
The waves are much stronger...
in the winter.
- Put everything down. - Gosh.
- We should go in first. - Let's do that.
It is really calm.
He can do it with his muscles.
- Surfing? - Yes.
Nice.
It's been so long. It's so exciting!
- Do you remember the hand gestures? - Which ones?
- If you do well... - Right.
Right. What was this?
"Give me a call."
No. It's the shaka sign.
- The shaka sign! - What's that?
This is the shaka sign.
What this means is, "You did well. You're amazing."
(A Hawaiian hand gesture that represents praise and encouragement)
- "Aloha" is also said with it. - Right.
This is what we'll use. I'll bring the board.
Let's get your foot tied before you get on it.
Your right foot.
Let's get your right foot.
It floats away if that isn't done.
Why?
- Because you might lose it. - The board might float away?
And if I sink into the water,
I have to get back...
- on the board. - Right.
- Si On should join us. - Si On!
- I'm going to paddle. - Okay. Get on top.
Lie on it.
- I think he'll be good at this. - He's so cute.
Paddle.
(Si On gets on the board skillfully.)
Isn't he the youngest surfer?
- He's learning at a young age. - Right.
- He looks like a prodigy. - Right?
- Right. - I thought that too.
Si On!
(He quickly gets to his uncle after paddling with his small arms.)
- Look at Mom. - There are no waves?
Get up. Paddle.
- I'm going to surf. - Okay. Get up. Paddle.
- Surf! - Get up.
(He carefully feels the water and gets up.)
- Gosh! - He gets into form right away.
- Gosh. - At that age?
- Gosh. - That isn't easy to do.
He's moving with the waves.
Gosh, that's so cute.
- Gosh! - My goodness!
- He looks like a penguin. - Gosh, that's so cute!
That's so cute.
(The 31-month-old child's feet stand firm on the surfing board.)
How cute.
That's so cute.
He's so small.
Go back to Dad.
(He comes down perfectly too.)
(That's amazing!)
Si On surfs too.
I saw photos and videos of him.
- Gosh. - He's bigger now.
- He was even younger back then. - Exactly.
- Gosh. - My goodness!
(Surfing genius Si On who rules the waves)
When did Si On start surfing?
Si On started...
- as soon as he turned two. - Gosh.
Right after his birthday.
He started right after learning how to walk.
You look amazing!
He has been surfing for more than half of his life.
- Right. - He's a master.
- He spent half of his life surfing. - Gosh.
You look amazing, Si On!
Blow him a kiss.
He wants to see his uncle do it.
You want to see me do it?
Watch carefully, Si On.
Show him what you've got.
He looks confident.
(My 31-month-old surfing genius nephew!)
Uncle will go now.
(Pay attention!)
(Your uncle...)
(has worked out!)
Show what your muscles can do.
Gosh!
- He's worse than me. - No.
I was just getting adjusted.
- You surf, don't you? - I'm pretty good.
Do you really surf?
I got lessons in Phuket for 50 dollars.
Really?
Have you learned anything in our country?
There's nothing he hasn't tried.
I'm this old. I've tried many different things.
That must be hard to do.
- It's hard. - It's hard.
You have to balance yourself on the water.
You have to have a good core.
His muscles are just good for watching.
He's not quite at that level yet.
- He hasn't reached that level yet. - Well,
to be honest, he's getting bigger along with his fat too.
(Rubbing)
- He's not there yet. - Even now,
- I'm a bit puffy. - Right.
I have a bit of fat around me.
- But that's what happens. - Right.
But that's just awful.
He falls off right away.
(Surprised)
He made that face when that happened.
(Splashing)
Did you see me, Si On?
(I did see you, Uncle.)
- Gosh. - My goodness.
Those are really fashion muscles.
(Watch me, Uncle!)
- He's good. - He's good.
Look at how stable he is.
- How is he so cute? - He's so cute.
(He casually shows a V unlike his uncle.)
Good.
(He comes down safely as well.)
- He's good. - Gosh.
I thought that he would be worse than me.
I've lived 13 times longer than him.
Why are you being jealous of Si On?
- Exactly. - It can't be helped.
It happens since it's something that I do as well.
I thought that I would be slightly better than Si On.
(Feeling competitive against a 3-year-old)
(I'm 38.)
- He has grown a lot. - He really has.
It's small. Hold onto it.
It's here.
- Where? - We can see it from afar.
The wave comes calmly.
So you're checking for the wave that's coming from afar.
- It's coming. - Press down.
One, two...
- Get up! - He did it!
(The muscular uncle finally stands with his two feet.)
He did it.
There you go. He did it.
There you go.
Nice one.
He's surfing by the sand.
(Sand)
The jumpsuit...
makes your body float.
The buoyancy makes your body float.
- It's the buoyancy. - Right.
(Laughing)
I was surprised since it was something so obvious.
One, two, three.
Press down as you get up.
One. Look forward.
Spread out your arms.
There you go. Okay. Come down.
Nice one! You did well!
(Nice one! You did well!)
(Shaka!)
(I'm good, aren't I, Si On?)
Show him the shaka sign.
- Uncle! - With his tiny hands.
Was that okay?
(Feeling proud)
(Feeling great)
I think that will be really exhausting.
You feel really hungry after two hours of that.
- Right. - You're about to die of hunger.
I went to a beach like that with a friend before.
We wanted to have the specialty of that region,
but there were only burger places.
- Right. - Right.
- It has the most calories... - Right.
and is something that can be eaten quickly.
- It saves time. - Right.
- There were a lot of burger places. - You're exhausted to eat.
You can take it off if you feel hot.
Really?
Should I try to look cool and take it off since it's hot?
Gosh.
You could get a tan too.
(Amazed)
(It's so refreshing!)
In my imagination,
I looked very sexy.
- The sun was out too. - You're not at that level.
- You're driving me crazy. - He's too pale.
- Gosh. - He's just unbelievable.
Excluding his legs,
he looks like a baeksuk with the top of his body.
He can be filled with rice through his bottom...
- and get his legs tied. - Right.
Right.
This is how I find out how I look.
- Boil it for a while. - It's a pale chicken.
(In my imagination,)
(I looked very sexy.)
The sun was out too. It was bright...
and it felt like songs of the summer were playing.
My muscles and abs were bulging out.
I just look like a native chicken.
Let's get a tan together.
Should we? Would that make me look better?
His face looks so serious.
(The place that makes me look sexy, the sea)
People might think you're in a surfing competition.
That's great though.
One, two...
- This song is playing? - Gosh.
(I've decided to come to the beach.)
(The sea...)
(waited for my sexiness!)
He keeps surfing by the sand.
(Why did I forget about this sea?)
Stop doing the shaka sign!
- Gosh. - Stop doing the shaka sign!
Turning around and doing that was horrible.
I'm struggling to watch myself too.
I'm getting reminded of the Palm Oil Family...
- body profile photoshoot. - Gosh!
That was better than this.
- I'm feeling so hot. - The one that isn't here.
- I feel so hot right now. - It's because you feel ashamed.
- I'm suddenly sweating so much. - There's no better way...
to feel hot than feeling ashamed.
(I've surfed well.)
Why do the shaka sign for that?
Again!
Why are you looking down?
What are you doing at a place that's like a lazy river?
It looks exactly like a lazy river.
(Swaying)
The waves are small.
Let's use the paddleboard, Jae Hyeon.
- Take the paddle. - Right.
Many people ride these.
- Right. - The waves were weak.
- That's better when waves are weak. - When the waves are weak,
- that's the best. - Really?
That looks like fun too.
Your knees should come here.
- Right here. - Okay.
Okay. Spread them out a bit more.
This is what you do.
Pick up the paddle.
Pick it up. Take a step with one foot.
The other foot now.
Get up on the board.
Hold the paddle like a walking stick.
Face forward. Look far away.
Keep your balance.
- Hold on. - Gosh.
- "The Old Man and the Sea!" - "The Old Man and the Sea!"
I've read that one.
- The marlin pops out. - Right. Hemingway's book.
That's perfect.
(A misunderstanding caused by his bad form)
(Standing awkwardly)
Hold on.
- I got it. - Should I hold it for you?
- Okay. I got it. - Okay.
Get your paddle.
Face forward.
- Gosh! - Face forward.
- Keep your balance. - Oh, gosh!
Gosh.
(Getting on his knees all of a sudden)
Uncle is doing slapstick comedy.
He's so cute!
Don't feel nervous. You can do it!
Right.
(Getting on his knees again)
He keeps making a deep bow.
I wasn't getting up with the help of the waves.
I had to get up exactly from that position.
- I see. - Even getting up is hard to do.
Earlier, the waves helped you get up.
I had to get up from that position and it was really hard.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- Gosh! - The ancestors of the sea.
Let's pray to the ancestors of the sea.
(I pray to the ancestors of the sea.)
Did you really work out?
(The surfing genius's anger)
"The surfing genius's anger."
I'll pull you if you're struggling.
- Gosh, the water is clear. - All right.
(They move to Bongsudae Beach with the paddleboard.)
- Follow me. - Just a moment.
Let's go!
(Let's walk there, Si On.)
Surfers...
move across the sea like that with the board.
As if it was public transportation?
It's like a water taxi.
That's amazing.
One, two.
- Keep the beat. - One, two.
Always face forward.
One, two.
- One, two. - There you go!
- He's on his feet though. - Right.
It was easier to stand with a bit more speed.
- There you go! - Right.
Hey,
this is a new world.
Gosh, the sea looks beautiful.
That looks great!
(A new world seen while being on the sea)
- That was really nice. - Check out the colors.
That looks incredible.
It feels like I'm flying.
- It's strange. - Right.
This is so exciting.
So that's how it's done.
It was a really strange feeling.
I was told to face forward without looking down.
Floating on top of the sea as if I was on an escalator...
felt so new.
It was something that I had never experienced before.
I think floating on a cloud would feel like that.
My legs felt so light.
I couldn't feel my weight at all.
(I couldn't feel my weight at all.)
- You're doing great. - I'm straining my feet so much.
(Moving around the sea as if it was the sky)
This is so exciting.
You use so much strength for this.
I'm feeling a bit scared.
I'll pull you if you come this far.
- See? He plopped down right away. - Gosh.
He's amazing. He's pulling him.
- He told me to hold onto his line. - Really?
- He's pulling you? - He's pulling me right now.
(Working hard to move 2 people)
There are so many fish in the sea!
(His legs have broken down.)
I can't see them.
You can't see them? They're right there.
I couldn't see them in the water.
Gosh, that's beautiful.
Your shoulders are so broad.
The weight of a dad.
Men living near the ocean are strong.
- That's right. - Of course.
- Fishermen are strong. - They're strong.
- Do you see the seawall? - I do.
This is fun.
How amazing.
You're just getting dragged from behind?
- It's a tour. - It looks fun.
- It's almost like... - Isn't it like a filial tour?
You should row too.
It looks like he's being exiled.
(A sinner being exiled to a faraway region)
- I can see myself in hanbok. - Yes, we can.
I can see myself in gat.
(Scholar Ahn being exiled for having a weak lower body)
- "I admire you, my lord." - I know.
"A better world will come."
You know those aristocrats.
- "A better world?" - "A better world will come."
"I admire you."
Exile?
Then he'll write a book at home.
- Yes. - Write a book?
Should I row with you?
No.
- It's deep here. - Is that so?
We have to go quite far.
(Sighing)
- Are you okay? - Get up already!
You're right.
They're here.
(Shaka)
Say hello to Uncle.
Hello.
We crossed the ocean to the other side.
- Gosh, that's amazing. - Say it again.
Si On walked there.
- Walk? - Si On walked there.
Shall we get going, Si On?
- Here you go. - All right.
- Let's go. Let's go, Si On. - Let's go.
(They return home while holding hands tightly.)
- The husband is at the back. - I know.
- Is he really a boatman? - I know.
Why would he walk separately?
(He joins them belatedly while carrying heavy stuff.)
What happens to men...
- when they go to the ocean? - I know.
(Sweet and considerate husbands of the ocean)
(Jae Hyeon comes out after washing away seawater.)
(Gosh, my back...)
- Did you hurt your back? - Gosh.
Because he used the muscles that he rarely uses.
(Coming inside Si On's place while grabbing his back)
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
- It sure was relaxing, but... - Yes?
Can you give me a pain relief patch?
A pain relief patch? Why?
I landed wrongly.
- I see. - I landed on my back.
He's right.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
- I must've been nervous. - Goodness.
Because I wanted to float,
- I tensed up. - You were tensed up.
- It can't be helped. - What is this?
This is a pain relief patch.
It's a medicine for Uncle because he's hurt.
I got it.
(Why are you sick?)
- You should've landed well. - Over here.
Being sick because I'm weak, because I'm skinny,
or because I work out, it's all the same.
That will last long.
I got physical therapy, and now...
You're getting physical therapy?
- I'm getting one now. - You got physical therapy?
After surfing?
Did you do mixed martial arts?
Why would you get physical therapy?
The pain lasted quite long.
(Even after bulking up, his muscles are super weak.)
There you go.
- We should eat now. - What shall we eat?
What do you want to eat, Si On?
Si On's favorite, pho.
- Pho? - Yes.
When I came here before,
you bought me king crab.
I'll make a dish for you this time.
- You're going to cook? - For Si On too.
I've looked into it,
and I wanted to make...
- scallop pasta. - That sounds delicious.
- Scallop is delicious. - I've already asked.
But you said Si On liked pho.
How about I use rice noodles for pasta?
That sounds pretty good.
Si On has never had pasta.
- Say, "Go." - Go.
- Go! Where to? - Where shall we go?
Go that way.
- The supermarket. With whom? - The supermarket.
- Who will you go with? - Are you going to go with Uncle?
Hold his hand.
- Give him a hug. - Goodness.
He's excited.
- That's so cute. - He's happy.
We've become close.
"We've become close."
(Overwhelmed)
I'll go to the supermarket with Si On.
- Sure, go ahead. - Go to the supermarket.
- I'll set things up. - Let's go to the market, Si On.
- See you later. - We'll be back.
See you later.
Si On, what kind of rice cake do you like? A white one?
Yes.
- Si On, do you like pho? - Yes.
- You like pho? - Yes.
Then shall we have pho and rice cakes?
Yes.
Si On, who do you like better, Mom or Dad?
(A sudden question)
He didn't answer.
He's become serious.
(Unresponsive)
Si On is blank.
(Lifting his head)
- Wait. Look. - What?
There's something there?
(Chirp)
There's something?
Let's do a shaka.
- Shaka. - Gosh.
- He's addicted to shaka. - Shaka.
- This is... - That darned shaka.
You did shaka to it?
You found something in common with him with shaka.
- That's right. - Yes.
- Gosh. Your pants came off. - Goodness.
He must've lost a lot of weight...
- after playing in the water. - Exactly.
You should take your pants off too to get closer to him.
You should form a bond of sympathy.
A bond of sympathy?
- Gosh. - Goodness.
(His pants came off in the blink of an eye.)
He must've lost a lot of weight...
- after playing in the water. - Exactly.
- His waist must've gone thinner. - Gosh, baby.
- Gosh, baby. - It must've helped get weight off.
I'm so glad it was Si On, not Jae Hyeon.
- Goodness. - That would've been bad.
Gosh, that scared me. That's...
It'd have been fun too if it were Jae Hyeon.
(Joking)
You should take your pants off too to get closer to him.
- That's right. - You become best friends.
You should form a bond of sympathy.
- A bond of sympathy? - That never occurred to me.
Hold on. Your hand...
Oh, no.
- Goodness. - How cute.
Were the pants too big?
Is it uncomfortable?
He's brave.
This side. There you go.
Let's go.
(You're all set. Let's go.)
(Laughing)
How cute.
The kid is brave.
- Yes. - Yes, he's somewhat strong.
(Kids of the sea are quite different.)
We're here.
Do you want to get on this?
(Lifting)
Let's sit you here.
Put your legs out.
Are your legs comfortable?
(Hold on, Uncle.)
Goodness.
There were holes for legs?
Si On put out his legs by himself.
- That's been around for a while. - Kids get on those.
There were such carts even when I was young.
That's more like a wagon.
- There were holes on the wagon. - Wagon?
How could wagons have holes for legs?
There were round holes on the wagon.
- I put out my legs through them. - That must've been the case.
- My dad would lift me like this. - Seriously.
- An A-frame. - An A-frame?
- An A-frame and... - They have lots of holes.
- It's different from a cart. - They're completely different.
- An A-frame. - Their functions are the same.
Shall we go?
(They enter the supermarket with Si On on the cart.)
How cool.
- Over there. - What's over there?
- Shall we go there? - Rice cake.
- What is he saying? - Rice cakes are over there?
Oh, rice cakes.
He likes rice cakes.
Kids that age like cookies.
They don't feed him. They don't feed him...
anything strong.
- They trained his appetite well. - Yes.
Gosh, there are so many rice cakes.
What's your favorite?
Which one is your favorite?
Which one would you like?
- I think he'll like... - Which one?
bar rice cakes the most.
- This one. Yes. - This one?
- Yes. - This one?
(Carefully chosen)
What is it? Sirutteok? A baby likes sirutteok?
- Even I don't eat that. - Wait. A baby likes sirutteok?
Well done.
You're holding that?
He has the appetite of a grownup.
There it is. Hello.
Sir, can I get two bags of scallop?
Two bags?
- Thank you for this. Thank you. - Thank you.
(He's done getting scallop for dinner.)
You're a good boy.
He's so cute.
- Why? - Gosh.
- He wants to eat it. - You want to switch hands?
Like this?
In case it falls?
- It's like a treasure for him. - Oh, my.
- He's unique. - He's carrying it like a plushie.
He would never let go of the rice cake.
(The kid of the sea secures the rice cake carefully.)
Choi Si On!
Daddy's over there, Si On.
- Dad? - He's up there.
Choi Si On.
Dad.
- Hurry over. - Okay.
How cute.
Let's go.
(He listens to his father and hurries home.)
Watch the step.
- Dad's here. - You're here.
What is that?
- Rice cake. - Is it rice cake?
Rice cake.
You got a big one, didn't you?
Should I wash these downstairs?
I set things up downstairs so you can wash there.
Let's go.
Help Uncle.
- You'll turn on the tap? - Turn on the tap for him.
- Wash them well. - All right.
Turn on the tap for me.
Here.
Put water in here.
Thank you.
(Skillfully providing water for him)
They're really solid.
Si On, try saying "solid."
Solid.
You're the best, Si On.
Say, "uncle."
Uncle.
(Perfect chemistry of Uncle and Si On)
All right. Let's go to Dad now.
(They finish washing scallops in no time as they worked together.)
He washes his hand.
He's good.
- He's smart. - He is.
I'll wash my hands too.
Good. Let's go upstairs.
Let's go upstairs, Si On.
(Showing off good teamwork and friendship)
(Carefully heading to the rooftop)
Gosh, what is this?
(A wide open space)
- That place is nice. - It's nice.
I could see the ocean and the mountain from up there.
(A view of a friendly fishing village unfolds.)
- You should watch him. - Shall I give you a hand?
He shouldn't come near the fire.
Hang out here.
I'll make the squid dish quickly.
(While Si On is hanging out with Uncle Jae Hyeon,)
(Min Ji quickly cooks.)
That's the best kitchen.
(Adding lots of ingredients she packed in small portions)
Did you always cook?
Me? No, I started after giving birth.
- Really? - Yes.
- My husband used to. - Really?
- They wouldn't deliver in? - Never.
- There's no delivery either. - I bet there's no delivery.
We've never fed Si On outside food.
- Really? - I made all the baby food too.
Your mom is amazing, so is your dad.
(Putting it in)
- Gosh. - That looks good.
Stir-fried squid?
That looks good.
I'm done.
It's a really healthy meal.
Spicy stir-fried squid pork.
(Shall I show off my cooking skills now?)
I'll start cooking now, so can you watch the baby?
(Adding scallops to the boiling water)
(Boiling)
That must be good. Goodness.
It must be really good.
Uncle is making something.
He's making pho, which you like.
Pho?
Yes, pho.
As for the recipe, everything is the same,
but I'm using rice noodles instead.
Make broth first using scallops.
Boil rice noodles separately.
For the last step, turn off the stove,
and use the broth for emulsion.
He knows what he's doing.
(Pouring the scallop broth into the pot)
(Boiling the rice noodles first)
(Stir-frying the rest in oil while the noodles get cooked)
(Sizzling)
I used whole garlic...
because the baby can't have it. I wanted to take it out later.
I see.
(Hold on, Si On.)
(I'll let you taste a fantastic flavor.)
(Focused)
(Crying)
(He starts whining as he's hungry.)
You want to go up there?
(I'm hungry, Uncle Jae Hyeon.)
He's throwing a tantrum now as he's tired.
He's hungry.
Uncle will make it quickly.
Uncle is making delicious pho.
(Glancing)
Four more minutes.
- Uncle? - I got it.
He'd feel rushed.
I know.
(He quickly prepares scallops.)
(As soon as he's done prepping them,)
(he adds them to the pan with oil.)
(Si On is waiting.)
Cover it with the lid.
- He's waiting. - The baby is hungry.
(Move the cooked noodles to the pan.)
Si On likes perilla oil, right? We were going to use that.
The kid likes perilla oil?
He loves adding perilla oil to pho.
Really?
(Crying)
- Say, "Feed me now, Uncle." - Say, "Feed me now, Uncle."
- "Feed me now, Uncle." - "Feed me now, Uncle."
(Let's hurry.)
(Si On is waiting.)
(Let's go, Uncle Jae Hyeon.)
- How cute. - I'm done.
He's done.
It's ready.
- Gosh. - It's ready.
What is this?
What?
- What is it? - Kids can't lie.
Look at that.
It's all soggy.
- Gosh. - That's rice noodles.
- Rice noodles get soggy fast. - It looks like kalguksu...
stuck at the bottom of a pot after having shabu-shabu.
I used rice noodles because Si On likes them.
- That's why I gave it a try. - If you were to use them,
you should've soaked them in water for 30 minutes.
- That's right. - Then stir-fried it on strong heat.
That's how pad thai is made.
- Like pad thai. - That's how pad thai is made.
- If you boil them... - They get soggy if you boil them.
(Jae Hyeon's rice noodle pasta is super soggy.)
(With Min Ji's spicy stir-fried pork,)
(the table is filled with food made with love.)
(Thinking)
They don't look happy.
It looks like you'll have to add ramyeon seasoning.
Sounds good.
Let's eat.
What is this? Gosh, what's this?
- What's that? - Please cut them small.
(Please cut them small for Si On.)
I'll give it to you later secretly.
- Oh, no. It's all soggy. - It's soggy.
(Soggy)
You can't eat that. Oh, no.
Taste it a little bit.
- Open wide. - Wouldn't it be good for digestion?
How is it? Open wide.
(Taking a bite)
- How is it? - Is he spitting it out?
(Spitting it out)
- Really? - Oh, my gosh.
Kids spit out bad food right away.
- Kids are more honest. - That's right.
I was really surprised.
Adults lie...
- and swallow it, at least. - I know.
(Trying it again for the sake of Uncle Jae Hyeon)
- He's eating it. - He's eating it.
He's spitting it out.
Si On, I used rice noodles for you.
I hope it turns out delicious.
It's a shame.
Si On never spits out food.
Maybe the texture is new to him.
I won't try it next time.
(Sorry. I won't try cooking next time.)
Should I wrap it with dried laver? Open wide.
(Should I wrap it with dried laver?)
Are you spitting it out?
- Is it bad? - Try a bite, at least.
(Hold on...)
There's something inside, right?
(He found the noodles hidden inside the dried laver.)
I should've used pasta instead.
(Fine. Since Uncle made it...)
He ate it. He ate it even after seeing it.
He's rinsing his mouth with water.
He just wants to swallow it.
Like medicine.
- That's right. - That's what I did...
when I was told to eat kimchi when I was young.
He's eating it because you made it.
- Do you want to try more? - Do you want to try more?
(Unresponsive)
I mean, the noodles are too...
- Goodness. - Gosh.
- Maybe scallops... - Dad.
Maybe scallops don't suit his taste.
That could be the case. Because it's seafood...
Si On has never tried scallops.
(Feeling bad for some reason)
(The dad tries a bite instead of Si On.)
It's not bad.
- Is it? - Yes.
- I want this. - You want this?
It's delicious.
- Is it? - Yes.
But seriously, it must taste okay.
How was it for you?
It didn't suit my taste either.
They said it was good.
It's because I made it.
They're angels.
- He just swallowed it. - He almost...
pushed it into his throat.
I know. He pushed it down to his stomach.
Just like how you swallow a big pill.
He put the chopsticks down into this throat.
So it wouldn't touch his tongue.
- They're good-hearted. - They're really nice.
- "Good-hearted." - They're good-hearted.
- It's a shame. - Let's just use pasta next time.
- The drink tastes good, right? - Si On, I'll make something good...
- next time. - I'll finish this.
- Have the drink. - Your cooking's got a lot better.
- Here. - This too.
I couldn't even make rice.
It was my first time seeing you cook.
- Does this taste okay? - It's delicious.
(Si On has rice wrapped with dried laver.)
Is that really Mount Seorak?
- Over there. - It's that side.
That's the one?
- I want to go to Mount Seorak. - How nice.
How long has it been since you moved here?
Has it been six years for Min Ji?
It's been ten years for me.
It's been almost five years for me.
- Five years? - Yes.
If Si On grows a little more,
will you move to the city?
- No. - You won't?
As for elementary, middle, and high school...
I like it better here.
- As for elementary school, - For high school...
even kids from Seoul and Gyeonggi Province move here.
- Really? - To live here.
There are many after-school activities here.
- I see. - Kids move there instead.
- That's right. - That's understandable.
Kids living here learn surfing for free.
- Really? - I see.
Golf and horseback riding.
- They learn horseback riding too? - Golf and horseback riding too?
Kids move to the country instead of moving to Seoul.
So that they can have proper education.
Since there's golf and horseback riding.
- That's right. - The spectrum is wide.
(There are more diverse educational environment options now.)
I think you won't have any worries...
if you live here.
I like how it's not loud here.
When you're floating on the ocean,
you flow naturally. I liked that feeling.
- When you float... - He likes it.
I know.
You know, though,
this scenery feels really strange.
- It feels foreign. - Why?
It's really fascinating how Min Ji became a mom.
- To that extent? - Yes, it's really fascinating.
She's a fool for her son.
(Heave-ho!)
- He's full of energy. - I know.
There are many kinds of fortunes,
but I think I'm really fortunate with people.
I say that because the more time goes by,
I feel more proud of my friends.
They're doing so well...
in a healthy way.
- That itself makes me happy. - He's right.
You know how we say, "Jackpot" when we find ginseng?
I'm just the ground,
whereas my friends are ginseng.
There are so many people I say "Jackpot" to,
so I'm really happy.
It's when the sunset is the prettiest.
- Goodness. - Gosh, it's pretty.
Si On, look at the sky.
- Goodness. - It's pink.
There's another reason for me to come here.
Si On.
We had fun by ourselves...
- back then. - That's right.
But having an additional member,
it's a different kind of fun.
I feel like Si On will grow really fast,
so I should come often.
- He grows really fast. - Kids grow so fast.
(Blessed with Good Relationships, Overflowing Happiness)
(Next story)
(A fresh and lively summer full of vitality)
(Dae Ho's vivarium is filled with vitality as well.)
(How will his rooftop look?)
(Gosh, how did it turn out this way?)
It rained so much.
(There was too much vitality.)
(Excessive spurt of vitality)
It twines as it goes up.
So even if I get rid of them...
(What's even worse is Damarghini wrapped with vines.)
How did this grow on a car?
(It must be possessed by the vine evil spirit.)
Gosh, it's so hot.
(Go away, evil spirit.)
(Revving)
(Damarghini, let's fly again.)
(Celebrating the extermination of the evil spirit)
(He refreshingly washes it as well.)
(What is this?)
(Why is it giving out this kind of color?)
(Damarghini is shedding black tears.)
(The evil spirit returned without dying.)
(I Saw the Evil Damarghini)
(Turning)
(An inexplicable movement)
(Stepping on the brake)
Oh, no.
(I'm going to get a driver's license today.)
(As Dudu's guardian...)
(She has to take him to the hospital if he gets sick.)
(I must have a driver's license.)
(Filled with fascinating equipment)
(A simulator training center for driving skills)
(Turning)
(Disqualified)
(A parade of minus points)
(What do I do?)
(Lee Jung, you should pull yourself together.)
(Can I try one last time?)
That's good.
(Awakened)
(Yes, nothing is impossible!)
(Maybe...)
(I'm a genius.)
(A driver's license test? I'll easily pass.)
All the good energy is coming to me.
(A truck?)
(Yes, let's give it a try...)
(getting a Type 1 driver's license.)
(Since that's cool.)
Let's start.
(I Am a Genius Type One Driver)